Iinari Expedition! Iinari Expedition!
Mijina! Star Rat in a short time!
Iinari Tokusan Dakchan!
I am Temine and Shinji Kitsune!
I'm looking forward to working with you!
Please! I'm Iinari Tokusan Dokusan!
Today, we are these two, right?
Yes!
Let's help Kikutani bookstore for today's expedition!
Please help us!
Today, we have a request from Kikutani Bookstore on the 6th floor of Eavins, and they need our help.
Yay! So I would like to go to the bookstore and ask them what they are going to do.
What are you going to do? Let's move on to Kikutani Bookstore!
Yes! Go!
Okay, well, we have arrived at Shukuya Bookstore.
It's amazing, isn't it?
There are all kinds of comic books,
Here we are at the Jojo's corner.
Amazing! Great!
Shingu-san, you like it, don't you?
Yes, I love it. I can't stop grinning.
How about you, Mr. Shimomi? What about Jojo?
I've seen it.
Really?
It's a VT manga that even girls know about.
I think Miyagi Prefecture residents must have seen it.
What part was it?
Four parts.
Four parts are in Miyagi Prefecture?
Yes, it's in M-City, Sendai City, Miyagi Prefecture.
May I ask you to stand up?
Seino.
Oh! It's very picturesque. As expected.
Also, the bookstore has a paper signing ceremony?
Hey!
Oh!
2,000 autograph papers signed by scholars?
Wow!
That means there are about 2,000.
That's amazing, isn't it? Look over there.
It's Dr. Oda's autograph!
He looks rather like a teacher in Murae City.
Oda Sensei, Sensei, Sensei.
It's displayed at the school's edge.
It's true.
That's true too.
I heard it's rather rare.
It's really amazing.
It's really amazing that it has Mr. Oda's autograph on it.
That means he touched it, right?
He did touch it, right?
Yes, his fingerprints are on it.
There are many other works.
There are so many.
So many signatures.
I feel like I need to come here just to see them.
Ah!
Here it comes!
Slam rank!
There's the SlamRank Corner.
All the goodness of SlamRank is here.
They put Micchan's quotes here, and he's a genius.
Plus, this, the legendary delivery of Lukawa and Sakurage.
You know, I can put this here.
I'm like, what are you going to do? Thank you for coming out here.
It's a little bit easier in the movie, right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And this one, I guess. What can I say?
I mean, it took a lot of work to make this.
This is in there, and it's already a great size.
I wish they would make one of these.
I'd like to have one made.
and my brother's.
I'm crying. I'm crying just looking at this.
Hitomi, are you pulling away?
No, I'm not.
I'll definitely read this when I get home.
If I'm in this corner...
You'll want to read it.
Muscle Man.
Muscle Man Corner.
That's great.
Hey...
You're not in the mood for this at all.
Muscle Man.
Buffalo Man!
Ramen Man.
Robin Man
To Sol Journey Phoenix
No, no, hey, temperature difference!
There's an E-Vingel on the first basement floor.
Yes, there is.
The Pinnickman Shop is...
Well, I've seen a lot of things.
I'm sure you'll be able to get some help from here.
I'll let you talk to the clerk.
Okay, now, I'll be taking care of you today.
Mr. Nakamura from Hikiya Shoten is here.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
I brought two people with me today.
Is there anything I can help you with today?
Hikiya Shoten Sendai is a bookstore in Sendai.
We put a lot of effort into this kind of pop-up decorations.
We put a lot of effort into that kind of thing.
Today, we'd like you to help us
I'd like to ask you to help us.
It's the face of the work.
Yes, the world view of the work.
Are you sure you don't mind if we do that?
Yes, by all means.
Today's topic is a popular manga by Koudansha.
Fragrant Flowers Bloom with Rin
I'm going to ask you to help me make a pop-up for it.
It's a popular manga.
Are you sure? Are you okay?
Will it hurt sales?
Yes, it's a liability.
Responsibility?
Let's work together.
I was wondering if I could help you make a pop-up for this now.
I'm getting nervous.
You're going to teach me how to do it.
We'll do it together.
I'm looking forward to working with you today.
Okay, let's start with you, Pearl.
Yes, please.
This is a pop-up.
I'm going to ask you to cut and paste the paper with the characters printed on it.
Use the scissors.
Use scissors to cut along the lines where it says "cut out".
I'll ask you to cut this blank space along the lines where it says "cut out".
After that, we will use double-sided tape to attach them.
Please be careful with the scissors.
I'm sorry, Pearl, you've never touched scissors or knives before.
She's a young lady who's never touched a scissors or a knife before.
Are you okay with that?
Be careful.
Careful?
Like you're going on a trip.
Be careful.
I'll see you later.
Good luck.
I'll do my best.
Well, then, Kitami-san...
Oh, Aizawa-san...
I'm counting on you.Please.
Mr. Aizawa, you seem to like books.
You seem to read a lot of books.
Mostly comic books.
What's your current favorite manga?
The one I mentioned today, by Paraharalines, is one of them.
But I also have a manga by a high dan player.
Hajimete no Ippo.
Yes.
First Steps in Folk Singing.
I like it a lot. Me too.
I'm reading it now and I'm really into it!
I'm wondering what's going to happen to Kazuho.
I wonder if he's going to come back or not.
I see.
Let's hear from Mr. Aizawa.
What do you do, Kitami?
In this manga.
There's a boy named Rintaro.
His family owns a cake shop.
So today, I'd like him to bake a cake.
With paper?
Yes, a chocolate cake out of construction paper.
I'm going to ask him to make a chocolate cake out of construction paper.
I'm a good cook.
Perfect.
Last month, the director of E-Beads sent me handmade Valentine's Day chocolates.
to the director of E-Beads last month.
Today, he lent them to me.
Where did I say that?
So, how do you do this?
It's all part of the plan.
I'm going to need you to follow it.
We'll build it so that it's concrete.
I see.
I'll take care of it.
I'll do my best.
I'll go.
Are you okay? Just like that?
Yes, ma'am.
You say that to make me nervous?
But if anything, this is a more difficult role for you. You know what you're doing.
Fukuya, you're a natural.
The role that comes naturally to you.
God is watching, isn't he?
I'm happy because I can cut while looking at the picture of the character like this
It's easy to cut.
You just cut and put them together?
Yes, it's supposed to be three-dimensional, so it takes time.
Yes, how long does it take to make this kind of sales floor, for example here?
Well, about 3 days at the earliest.
I see.
On average, it takes about a week.
What is design?
There are about 3 or 4 people in charge of designing the hop.
We have about 3 or 4 people in charge of the hop, and they make the initial design in their minds.
After that, we print the book documents and so on.
And then they make these little things.
Wow, Sega Satter, I miss it.
We put all these things together in the end.
It takes about a week to do all of this.
I see.
That's an average time.
So you would say that the person in charge is free to do as he/she pleases.
Yes, to a certain extent, it is left to the discretion of the person in charge.
Are there any contests like this held at bookstores nationwide?
Yes, there are many contests.
I have won many contests.
When I win, I receive a letter of commendation from the author of the book.
I see.
And sweets as prizes.
Yes, there are such perks.
For example, the reason I'm helping you today...
It has nothing to do with the contest?
Yes, in fact, there is a contest for this year's work as well.
I have some great information for you two right now from Mr. Nakamura.
I heard that there is a contest for this piece that we are going to make today.
What kind of contest?
It's a display created by bookstores all over the country.
Publishers and teachers will actually see these displays.
The teachers will actually look at these displays and rank them accordingly.
So the work I'm helping with today will be part of the contest, right?
Yes, it's a contest.
What do you do?
I didn't even know I entered.
Then don't cut off his head or anything.
Sure thing.
I'll get in trouble.
My hands are shaking.
But you've already decided on the overall design, right?
Yes, we're asking you to help us with a part of it.
If you want to add a little of our flavor to it, for example, that's fine.
That's fine.
What?
Really?
I don't know how.
I've never done it before.
This is getting a little nerve-wracking, isn't it?
I've been working hard.
How many books does Kikuya have now?
How many books do you have?
The selection is amazing.
We have about 200,000 books.
200,000 books?
Most of them are comic books, subculture, occult literature.
Orchids, hobbies...
It's a whole world out there.
It's at such a level that there's not a comic book I can't find!
Happiness
Oh, it's merged!
It's beautiful. It's wonderful.
You're good at it.
Okamoto san is good at giving compliments
No, no, no, it's true
But you're right, it's good.
Are you sure it's not out of place?
Yes, not at all. It's perfect.
Great, perfect.
Excellent.
Okamoto san, you're so good
You could be an elementary school teacher.
It's done, isn't it?
It's done!
After this, we'll cut the margins.
Leave a few millimeters of white space
I want the scissors to follow this outline.
Great!
It's starting to look like a chocolate cake.
It totally looks like chocolate cake.
Okamoto-san, are you familiar with Ibinari Tohoku-san?
Yes, I have.
Really?
I like Momokuro.
Stardust Promotion is the same.
That's right.
That's why I knew a little bit about you.
Next time you have a big view at Ibins, I'd love to see it.
Yes, I'll be there to cheer you on!
Yay!
Please give my best regards to Shinji Nanamizu and Kitami Hair Salon!
Especially...
There are 7 other people here.
Don't worry about it.
I think it's fate that these two are here today.
It's done!
That's it!
You're good.
That's great!
It was really hard to whip the cream!It was so hard to whip the cream.
What are you talking about?
It's paper.
Paper.
Very good! Beautiful!
I guess Kitami-san's work is done for now.
Yes.
As expected, as expected.
Steady!
It's done!
Thank you!
Rintaro-kun is done!
How do you like the cake Rintaro made?
Do you think it's okay, Auntie?
Yes, it's fine. It's perfect!
Perfect!
I'd like you two to add a little color.
Is that okay?
Okay, Ms. Chinami and Mr. Chi.
I'd like you to make a pop-up saying
I'd like you to make a pop-up that says "recommended".
I see!
Good idea, Ms. Chinami.
It's very dense, isn't it?
Very dense!
Okay, then.
Yes! Ready!
Ta-da!
I recommend it!
I made a chocolate cake earlier, so I made a chocolate cake.
I made a chocolate cake earlier, so I scratched chocolate on it!
Yes, yes, yes!
I'm giving a little bit of a Northeastern feel with this Daccha, right?
I'm a pearl!
If you see this at the contest, you'll be like, "Hmm? If you don't know it, you're not going to like it.
If you don't know it, you should see it.
I think it's a must-have for your name.
You're showing too much color.
It's a pearl.
Yes, it's in there with my regards.
That's good, both of you.
Mr. Nakano, what do you think of this?
Oh, wow! So cute!
What's this?
You're so sweet.
I'd buy it in a second if I saw it!
Wow!
Are you okay? Like this.
It's good.
Yay! Yes!
Now, I'd like you to put this in the corner.
Yes!
Let's move to the corner.
Amazing!
This is handmade.
Wow!
Amazing!
Did you make this?
Yes, I made it.
Wow!
Salon and Aizan, right?
Ha-ha-ha!
Please put the chocolate cake you made in this box.
Excuse me.
Yes, sir.
I see. So this is how it's going to be.
Sami's cake has just arrived.
It's 350 yen. Chocolate cake.
I made a 350 yen cake.
It looks like this.
Wow!
Wow! Amazing!
I'll have them put it up.
Oh! It's done!
That's great!
Lastly, I'd like to show you the recommendation pop-up that you just wrote.
Eh!
Put it on your favorite cake!
Wow!
That's great! Where should I put it?
I think it should be on my chocolate cake.
Here?
A fan from the Northeast came to see me.
Chocolate cake made by Rinne!
For 350 yen, he can't buy it, right?
That's right.
Ah.
Just a feeling.
Thank you.
You can take pictures, right?
Yes, I can take pictures.
That's enough.
Okay, everyone take a picture.
Spread the word about my cakes and cartoons.
Yes, I'll do that.
I'll put them up.
I wrote "in the back".
The one at the back.
Especially the chocolate cake at the back!
It's done!
I bought it!
It's good!
It looks like a store!
It fits in!
No other store has this idea, right?
Hey! It's too good!
If I could do it forever with the help of two people, I would!
Wow! Thank you!
That's great! Now it's complete!
I'm impressed! I'm really impressed!
How do you like it when you see it finished?
It's even better than I thought it would be.
I'm so happy to be a part of it!
I'm always looking at this section of the site.
I can't think of anything else that I've cut even a little bit
I can't even think about it anymore!
It's just too much! I'm so happy!
It makes me want to read it! I can't wait to read it!
I wonder what the story is about!
Hey! Amazing!
Well, today, I visited Chikuya Bookstore on the 6th floor of B-Benz and helped them out.
I'd like to thank you again for your help.
Thank you very much for helping us and making such wonderful clothes!
Thanks to you two, we have created a wonderful corner.
By the way, Ms. Nakamura, what is this contest?
Well, I applied in the middle of March.
I don't know when the results will be announced, but I don't know the details yet.
By the way, I don't know how long it will be on display or how long it will be on display.
The exhibition is going to be up for at least a month, right?
I think we visited Chikuya Bookstore to help out.
Please visit our store!
Thank you very much for your time today.
Bye bye!